[
     {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 27?",
      "correctAnswer": "729",
      "options": [
        "731",
        "729",
        "734",
        "727"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "25",
      "options": [
        "30",
        "23",
        "25",
        "27"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "9",
        "11",
        "14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 15?",
      "correctAnswer": "225",
      "options": [
        "225",
        "227",
        "230",
        "223"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "11",
        "9",
        "14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 28?",
      "correctAnswer": "784",
      "options": [
        "789",
        "782",
        "786",
        "784"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 18?",
      "correctAnswer": "324",
      "options": [
        "322",
        "324",
        "329",
        "326"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "100",
      "options": [
        "100",
        "98",
        "102",
        "105"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 21?",
      "correctAnswer": "441",
      "options": [
        "439",
        "446",
        "441",
        "443"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 37?",
      "correctAnswer": "1369",
      "options": [
        "1371",
        "1369",
        "1374",
        "1367"
      ]
    }
]